artsjournal.com 2006-10-20

# Privacy Policy - ArtsJournal About Us: Daily Arts News

Updated: August 20, 2002

**INTRODUCTION**

Artsjournal respects your right to personal privacy and takes your privacy seriously. When we collect your personal information and personal history information, you can be assured that we will handle it in a manner that will ensure its protection and security from unauthorized access or disclosure. Artsjournal is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site. 

This document describes our privacy and security practices. BY PARTICIPATING IN OUR WEB SITE, OR OTHERWISE PROVIDING US WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU ARE ACCEPTING ALL PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY & SECURITY DOCUMENT. THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS IN THIS PRIVACY & SECURITY DOCUMENT ARE SUBJECT TO UPDATE WITHOUT NOTICE, SO PLEASE REVIEW THEM PERIODICALLY. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE ARTSJOURNAL WEB SITE SUBSEQUENT TO ANY AND ALL POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY & SECURITY DOCUMENT WILL MEAN THAT YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE TO ACCEPT ALL CHANGES. Please note that anonymous data from which you cannot be identified is excluded from the restrictions described in this Privacy & Security document.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Our goal at Artsjournal is to provide all Web site users with the highest quality Web site experience and user services. In order to ensure that you receive the highest quality user services, and to make certain we provide the highest quality experience possible while you participate and interact on this Web site, we collect certain personal information and personal history information directly from our Web site users.

You can visit the Artsjournal Web site without identifying yourself or providing any personal information. At certain times, however, we may ask you to provide certain information that will enable us to provide you with important product services, enhance your Web site experience, or enable us to follow up at a later date. Your participation is completely optional. For example, we request information when you subscribe to our newsletter or mailing list. Artsjournal does not use cookies or allow advertisers or sponsors to use cookies.

For each visitor of our Web site, our web server automatically recognizes the visitor's IP address/domain name combination. 

We collect IP address/domain name combinations of visitors to our Web site, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate and user specific information on what pages visitors access or visit and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or personal information requested for site registrations, etc. 

The information we collect may be used to improve the content of our overall Web site, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify visitors about updates to our Web site, and/or used by us to contact visitors for marketing purposes. 

**PRACTICES INVOLVING CHILDREN**

Artsjournal is committed to ensuring and providing a safe environment for all children. As such, please read our policies regarding children under the age of 13 years old. Artsjournal's Web site is a general audience Web site. As a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 years of age, please determine the appropriateness of granting access to Content on this Web site to your child. 

If you are under the age of 13 years old, you should not provide any personally identifiable information to Artsjournal without the knowledge and consent of your parent or legal guardian. If we learn that you are under the age of 13 years old, we will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you without the verifiable consent of your parent or legal guardian, except as allowed by law.

We collect personally verifiable information directly from Web site users/visitors. We do not collect this information without the knowledge of the user/visitor. 

**LINKING AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

The Artsjournal Web site may feature links to third party Web sites. There may be occasion where access to this site is provided by a link from a third party site. Such links may take the form of text links, advertisements, banners, buttons, integrated gift services, digital cash, digital gift certificates or otherwise. THE GOODS AND SERVICES AVAILABLE THROUGH THESE LINKS ARE OFFERED BY COMPANIES INDEPENDENT OF ARTSJOURNAL. ARTSJOURNAL MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS AS TO QUALITY, FITNESS, WORKMANSHIP, VALUE, APPROPRIATENESS, OR RELIABILITY OF MERCHANDISE AVAILABLE THROUGH THESE LINKS OR REPRESENTATIONS AS TO BUSINESS PRACTICES OR SOLVENCY OF THESE COMPANIES. ARTSJOURNAL DOES NOT ENDORSE AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OR THE CONTENT OF SUCH WEB SITES AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY ASSOCIATED WITH THEIR USE AND CONTENT OF ALL SUCH SITES.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our sponsors and advertisers. This information is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual visitor or computer accessing the Artsjournal Web site. Such general information enables us to help our advertisers better understand the traffic patterns of our site.

This is the Web site of Artsjournal. 

Please contact Artsjournal by e-mail at: [mclennan@artsjournal.com](mailto:mclennan@artsjournal.com)
